Let's talk about the leading elements from to the array.
Consider this array, this matrix.
And we have these elements, and we need to remove that first, that the one arrived at index one and
two, which means that the second row and the third column, so I need to remove number seven and put
it to integer the minimum value.
There is no direct manipulation of a code that removes the code that element and shifts the element
position of the other elements inside an array.
So think about it if I removed seven from this.
From this 2D array, then eight would not become or would not contain remains in the same position.
It will be shifted to the left.
So think about it.
If I changed it into a rip and replace it seven, so I need 41 to replace eight now.
Forty eight, forty one is not is not remaining in the third row.
It will become in the second row.
So it goes up.
And this is a this is a very bad because I don't need to shift all the elements.
This is not like the deleting an array, an element from array of single dimension.
It is not the same counts like deleting that element and shifting the elements, the other animals to
its position.
No, it's not the same at this.
It's just replacing the code.
They're replacing the No.
What we have, what we are going to delete with the integer, the minimum value, or there is another
way to put it with minus one, but we prefer putting an integer that many more value.
So if I need to remove these two elements at the third that position the fourth row and the second or
the third column, I need to put an integer that minimum value and this is what we prefer.
Now let's go to the code.
So in order to delete element from two the array, we need to surround it with triet catch and system
that print deleted successfully if we have put the integer dot minimum value.
So I'm assigning Arrow, a specific cell at index row and index column that we specify to an integer
that minimum value, which is in the inside, which is included inside that Java JDK.
OK.
Or at the other systems like C or Python.
This is very simple.
I am just like updating the elements.
It's about updating the elements to integer the minimum value.
OK.
There is no deletion by by removing the elements and shifting the others to its place.
It's not like the first one to one the array.
OK.
This is very simple.
No, it's at this time complexity is all of one.
I need from you to understand that there is no dilution by means of the listing element, but it is
updating the elements to a minimum value or other value that you may consider it if you are storing
positive values inside a matrix.
If you see minus one or minus 10 or minus fifty five, then you know that this element has been removed.
So it will not be red inside.
Therefore, look that you are rating just positive values.
OK.
This is the algorithm behind the leading.